https://thecostumecloset.com/privacy-notice/

Loading the content...
Contact Us
Uncertainty? We can help (click here...)
Need Help?Call (972) 400-1282 or Email Us
Prefer a paper order form? Download a printable order form  for emailing or faxing.
Make our costume closet YOUR costume closet! Follow us to stay connected!
(Click HERE to see larger image)
Large Team? No problem!
Large team sets!
Privacy Notice
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for TheCostumeCloset.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Use of Website Cookies
We utilize “cookies” (aka “HTTP cookie”, a text file stored in your browser) for web traffic analysis and to aid in better performance of some of the dynamic elements of the website experience (for example, the shopping cart).
Third parties whose services we utilize, such as website analytic service providers, may collect information about a visitor to our site. This information often is aggregate data.  Individual information of this type is tied to a browser or device and not specific identifiers such as the visitor’s name and address.
Personally Identifiable Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email, a website form, or other direct contact from you. We do not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request.
Your Access to and Control Over Contact Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via our contact form or the phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any contact data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as personal contact information), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via our contact form or the phone number given on our website.
Rental orders require a $100 minimum purchase. Read more about Rental Agreement terms and conditions
Search for:
Search
Privacy Notice
© 2015-present, The Costume Closet. 705 N. Bowser Rd., Suite 108, Richardson, TX 75081
Mobile version:
Enabled
Back to top
Search
Use the search box to find the product you are looking for.
×
Login
Username or email *
Password *
Lost Password?
Create Account
×
Cart
No products in the cart.
